大家安安 怎么样啊
Hey, all y'all. What's going down?
我对你的意见
My opinion of you.
就是戴个假眼镜是闹哪样
What's with the fake glasses?
对戴真眼镜的人来说 你这样太无礼了
As an actual glasses wearer, this is offensive.
就好像没残疾的人把车停在残疾人专用车位
It's like non-disabled people who park in handicapped spaces.
我进去出来就借停了三分钟 小姑娘
I was in and out in three minutes, young lady,
而且我是去拿你的针眼药
and it was your stye medication I was picking up.
手链有点多啊 小子
That's a lot of bracelets there, buddy.
不用管她们 是她们太胆小了
Just ignore them. They're being sheep.
如果我以前也老是在意别人说的话
If I'd listened to what other people said,
90年代我根本不可能弄那个酷炫的发型
I'd never have rocked my '90s frosted tips.
我们还有照片
We've got pictures.
才没有呢
No, we don't.
你是独一无二的 儿子
You're an original, son.
上天创造你的时候 没用模具做
When they made you, they broke the mold.
好吗 卢邓
What's good, L.D.?
当然
Yo, will.
卢克 这样问可能不太好
Luke, um, there's no easy way to ask this.
你是加入什么男团了吗
Are you in a boy band?
我们要去码头耍
So, we're gonna go hang at the pier.
你去吗
You in?
好像不错 但我可能去不了
Sounds cool, but I don't know if I can.
没错 我们今天有很多事情
That's right. We got a big day planned.
他要来给他老爹打工
He's coming to work with the old man.
抱歉
Sorry.
下次吧
Next time.
债贱[再见]
Deuces.
债贱
同意[跟你们的妈妈说吧]
Word to your mothers.
说真的 大卫 替我跟你妈打个招呼
Seriously, David. Tell your mom I say hi.
她来啦 我们的小天才
There she is -- our little genius.
看看我认真的小姑娘
Look at my conscientious little girl
提早一天就开始准备去上大学
getting ready to leave for college a whole day early.
我今天就走
I'm leaving today.
-什么 -不要啊
- What? - No.
不不不 不行 我们都计划好了
No, no. No, no. We have a plan.
我打算晚餐给你做你最爱的菜
I-I was gonna make your favorite meal for dinner,
然后我们因为分离焦虑会吵架
and then we were gonna fight because of separation anxiety,
然后明天早上
and then tomorrow morning,
我们会在你离家之前又和好
we would make up before you leave for good.
-我就... -不行不行
- I just -- -Oh! No, no,
各位 所以我才没有告诉你们
guys, this is exactly why I didn't tell you!
但我不能送你去学校啊 我今天有房子开放日
But I can't take you. I have a showing.
我准备要刻离别歌曲盘在送你的路上放呢
I was gonna burn a CD of goodbye songs for the ride.
我对我的决定感到前所未有的满意
I have never felt better about a decision.
我学校离家里就30分钟车程
Look, I'm only 30 minutes away,
而且我过几个星期就回来了
And I'll be back in a couple of weeks.
我已经让海莉送我过去了
I already asked Haley to take me.
我该走了
Well, I better get going.
你们每个人可以抱我5秒钟
You may each hug me for five seconds.
我想告诉你 你永远是我的小姑娘
I want you to know that you'll always be my little girl.
再见...
Goodbye, nor--
时间到了 老妈
Time's up. Mom.
我好为你骄傲
I am so proud of you,
我知道你会取得伟大的成就
and I know you're gonna achieve great things in this world,
我最近读到有一种新甲油
and I just read about this new nail polish that changes colors
如果你把指甲放进有迷药的饮料 就会变色
if you dip it in a drink that has a roofie --
-下一位 -我不用了
- Next. -I'm good.
那好吧 很好
All right, cool.
我到了会给你们发短信的
Well, I will text you guys when I get there.
他的5秒钟给我
I'm taking his five seconds.
彻底悲剧 没别的形容方式了
It's a tragedy -- no other way to put it.
本来多美好的一天
Such a beautiful day, too.
只要学着接受莉莉有足球比赛
We just have to accept that Lily has a soccer game
我们都得去观赛就可以了
and we all have to be there.
你早该找个借口的
You were supposed to make an excuse.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry!
我在集市上碰到小卡
I ran into Cam at the market.
他问我们能不能去 我就慌了
He asked if we could go. I panicked.
我自作自受[朝自己脚开一枪]
I shot myself in the foot.
是啊 你朝你的脚上开了一枪
Oh, yeah, you shot yourself on your foot,
你把脚放进自己嘴里[说错话]
You put your foot in your mouth,
你鞋子穿错脚了
you put the shoe in the wrong foot.
你们美国人为啥什么都要扯到脚啊
What is with you Americans and the foot?
顺便说一嘴 我讨厌那幅画
I hate that painting, by the way.
我要去把最后一个可颂甜甜圈吃掉 我太难过了
I'm having the last cronut. I'm so depressed.
抱歉 孩子 安迪已经给吃掉了
I'm sorry, kid. I think Andy ate it.
比赛2点开始是吗
So the game starts at 2:00, right?
是杰吃掉了最后一个可颂甜甜圈
Jay ate the last cronut.
没人喜欢告密者哦 小孩
No one likes a tattletale, kid.
谢谢你这么诚实 宝贝
Thank you, baby, for being so honest.
所以我们一小时后出发
So we should leave in about an hour.
什么"我们"
What is this "we"?
我得去给乔注册冬令营
I have to go and register Joe for the winter camp.
妈咪要去买鞋子
Mommy's going to buy shoes.
我可没养一个叛徒
I did not raise a rat!
没人逃得过
Nobody gets out of this.
世界上最糟糕的运动 世界上最糟糕的运动员
World's worst sport, world's worst players of it.
22个小女孩挤成一团
22 girls in a cluster
像个坏掉的吸尘器一样之字形穿过球场
Zig-zagging across a field like a busted roomba.
唯一吸得起来的就是我宝贵的两小时
Except the only thing it sucks up is two hours of my life.
看吧 这座卖不出去的房子
Behold, the unsellable house.
挂牌2年了
Two years on the market,
已经击溃了城里所有房地产代理人的心
It's crushed the soul of every real-estate agent in town.
陶德与泰瑞·泰勒 那对卖房子的夫妇
Todd and Terry Taylor, the spouses selling houses --
现在都离婚了
They're no longer either.
我以前很喜欢跟着我爸爸
I used to love going to work with my dad
去他的杂货店工作 弗兰克食品镇
to his grocery store, Frank's Food Town.
我喜欢看他切断了一根手指
I got to watch him crack up the deli team
把熟食窗口的人逗得捧腹大笑
by pretending to lose a finger,
他可以从橘子金字塔里抽出一个来
Or he'd pull out an orange from the pyramid
但金字塔不会倒
and somehow, it wouldn't fall.
我才不管外面的招牌说什么
I don't care what the sign out front said --
省钱才不是王道 我爸才是王
Savings wasn't king. My dad was.
艾丽克斯走了
You know, with Alex leaving,
咱俩就有更多时间在一起了
you and I are gonna get to spend a lot more time together.
等等
Wait.
这是什么玩意儿
What the whatsit?
这是鸭蛋呢
Those are duck eggs.
好酷
Cool. So --
还记得咱俩以前老说要养小鸭子吗
Remember how you and I used to talk about raising ducklings
然后给它们建个小鸭戏团
and building them a little bird circus?
好像吧
Kind of.
你觉得我们今天要在这里待多久
How long do you think we're gonna be here today?
我喜欢你要说的东西
I like where you're going with this --
搞个限时挑战
Make it a time challenge.
我觉得我可以在...
I think I can get her done
在五小时之内卖出
in under five hours.
那样我们应该有足够的时间去蹦床公园了
That'll leave us time to get to the trampoline park.
对了 惊喜
Oh, and surprise.
我们要去蹦床公园了
We're going to the trampoline park.
啵嘤[弹跳声]
Boing!
他这一生将会被...
His life will be rem--
不对
No.
最近家里很忙
So, busy time at the house lately.
有趣的忙
Fun busy.
我接了一些工作
I've taken on some work
帮人们处理财产和遗嘱
helping people with estates and wills.
比我想象中要更悲伤
It's sadder than I thought it would be.
有趣的悲伤
Fun sad.
-不不 别开枪 -砰砰砰
- No, no, don't shoot! - Bang, bang, bang, bang!
不
Oh, no!
我要死了 我要死了
I'm dying! I'm dying!
同时 我也开始经营一个副业
Meantime, I'm running a side business we started
短期出租我们楼上的公寓
doing short-term rentals on our unit upstairs.
我们自称为"艺术房客"
We call ourselves the artful lodgers.
米奇尔 当你填写
Mitchell, by any chance
新的出租协议时
when you were filling out the new rental agreement,
你是不是忘了标注不许携带宠物 尤其狗
did you forget to mark no pets, or, specifically, dogs?
真抱歉
Sorry, sorry, ooh!
记得唐纳森一家吗
You remember the Donaldsons?
这真是要了命
This is a vanderkoff.
有些夫妇可能会感受到压力
You know, s-some couples might feel the strain
互相撒气
and take it out on one another.
但是艺术房客们可不会
But not the artful lodgers.
今早挺艰难的
This morning was tough.
好了好了
There, there.
等你准备好了 在这里和这里签字
And whenever you're ready, there and there.
姑娘们 不不不
Girls. No, no, no.
现在时间不合适
Not a good time, not a good time.
大爸不是该载你们去比赛吗
Wasn't daddy supposed to be driving you to our game?
大爸在忙着处理着
Daddy's been a little bit busy himself dealing with linens
从未被人抱怨过"粗糙"的亚麻织物
that no guest has ever called scratchy before.
有办法让房间里暖一点吗
Is there a way to make the room not so cold?
你知道早上在你丈夫身边醒来
Do you know what it's like to wake up
而他冷得和冰一样的感觉吗
next to your husband one morning and he's cold as ice?
知道
Yes.
你吃早餐的时候我来处理
Yeah, I'll work on that while you eat breakfast.
你做了法国吐司了吗
Did you make the French toast?
做了 在桌子上
Yes, it's right on the counter.
-那是法式吐司 -怎么回事
- That's French toast. - What's happening?
我想要法国人吃的普通吐司
I wanted regular toast for the French people.
那你该说清楚啊
Surely there was a better way to describe that.
他对蛋过敏 米奇尔
He's allergic to eggs, Mitchell.
你为什么吃啊
Wh-- okay, w-why did you eat that?
他为什么还吃啊
Why -- why did he eat that?
也许我们该找另一个时间完成此事
Okay, maybe we should finish this up another time.
告诉你一声
And just so you know
其他人有需要欢迎推荐我
I do -- I do work on referrals.
有一间房间你会很喜欢的
Here is a room you're going to love --
你的男人基地... 衣橱
Your very own man ca--closet.
男人衣橱
Man closet.
谁喜欢地下室啊
Who loves, uh, basements?
我只是问着玩的
That's a rhetorical question.
这里有一间地下室
Have I got a basement for you.
下来时注意脚下
Watch your step coming down.
这间地下室已经装修完毕了
Because it's a finished basement,
你们可以看看这里有多大面积
You can actually count the square --
我觉得这栋房子不适合孩子住
I don't think this house is kid-friendly.
我们用攀登绳
Well, you said it yourself
爬进车道时 你就这么说了
when we were taking the towrope up the driveway.
这房子看起来像是奇怪的宇宙飞船
This -- this house looks like a weird spaceship.
孩子们都喜欢宇宙飞船
Kids love spaceships.
对吧 卢克
Don't they, Luke?
是啊
Yeah.
我记得有一天 那时候我还跟卢克差不多大
I remember one day, I was around Luke's age,
我不大高兴在我爸店里待着
and I wasn't all that happy to be at food town,
但我爸爸知道该怎么做
but my dad knew exactly what to do.
他去找宣传员
He gets on the P.A.
说 注意了 购物者
And he says, "Attention, shoppers,"
然后他把麦克风给了我
and then he hands the mike to me.
我吃了一惊
I was like, "What?"
"红翼花生酱 1.69元两瓶"
"Red wing peanut butter -- $1.69 for two."
他在那次促销中损失了很多钱
He lost a lot of money on that sale,
但那种激动的感觉我绝对不会忘记
but it's a rush I'll never forget.
就像是在潜水艇上一样 对吧
It's like being on a submarine, right?
你们是汤姆·克兰西的粉丝吗
You guys, uh, fans of Tom Clancy?
让卢克带你们参观完吧
You know what? Luke'll finish the tour.
是办公室的电话
It's the office.
-你手机都没响 -到你表现的时候了
- It's not ringing. - This is your moment.
喂
Hello?
跟我来吧
Follow me, I guess.
我们怎么上二楼
How did we get on the second floor?
很棒吧
Isn't it great?
有个觉察不到的斜坡
There's an imperceptible rise.
你们要么掉头
So you guys can either reverse course
要么轮流顺着滑竿滑下去
or take turns sliding down the fireman's pole.
卢克会演示的
Luke'll show you.
等等
H-hang on.
因为你不让爸妈为你哭
But because you wouldn't let mom and dad cry over you,
他俩的情绪会憋在心里
that emotion is gonna build up
然后在我和卢克身上爆发
and explode all over Luke and me.
抱歉 我只是等不及了
I'm sorry. I just couldn't want.
你知道我等今天等了多久吗
Do you know how long I've been dreaming about this day?
离开你家人的那天吗
Leaving your family?
别说得像是我侮辱人一样
Don't turn it into an insult.
我只是准备好了
I'm just really ready for this.
我身边终于都是聪明有求知欲的人了
I'm finally surrounded by smart, curious people.
好吧
Okay.
我要走了
So, I'm gonna go.
你好 你肯定是艾丽克斯
Hi! You must be Alex.
我是你的室友梅西
I'm your roomie. I'm Maisie.
我爸爸说那是棒极了的缩写 但其实不是
My dad says it's short for amazing, but it's not.
-等等 我选了另一个 -室友 我知道
- Wait, I-I picked a different -- - Roommate, I know.
她生病了 她恐慌症发作了
She got sick -- Well, she had a panic attack.
我同情她 我来大姨妈之前也会这样
I can sympathize. I usually get one right before my cycle.
总之 他们拒绝了她的签证 她还在挪威
Anyways, they denied her visa and she's still in Norway.
救命 出不去了[挪威]
"Help! There's norway out."
你多大了
How old are you?
我15岁了 但我看过4部R级电影了
I'm 15, but I've seen four R-rated movies already.
你来了我好激动
I'm so excited you're here.
我该把药放哪儿啊
Where should I put my medicines?
你可以走了 我没事了
Yeah, so you are good to go. I'm fine.
等下
Oh, not quite yet.
梅西 你会说他国语言吗
So, Maisie, do you speak any languages?
西语 法语 俄语 德语 还有伍基语[星战]
Si, Oui, Da, Ja, and of course I also speak wookiee.
这一定会很有趣
Ahh! That is gonna be so much fun!
是啊
Yay!
他们才住了两天就用了十八条毛巾
They've been here 2 days and they've used 18 towels,
却完全没有碰过肥皂
yet the soap is untouched.
他们是像大象一样互相蹭干净吗
What are they -- sloughing each other clean like elephants?
米奇尔 太好了 你来了
Mitchell. Great, you're here.
查克教练家里有人去世了
Coach Chuck had a death in the family.
多谢你能记得介绍我生意
Thank you so much for remembering about the referrals.
我现在没带名片 但是...
I don't have a card on me right now, but --
不是 是他不能来
No. He can't come,
由于你是助理教练
and since you're the assistant coach,
现在由你带队
you're in charge.
好吧
Okay.
你应该没问题吧
Think you're gonna be okay with that?
助理教练跟教练又有多大区别呢
Assistant coach, coach. What's the big diff?
从一名真正教练的角度看 确实不一样
Well, as an actual coach, um, diff.
拜托 今天就是来享受新鲜空气的
Come on, today's about being out in the fresh air,
抛开家里那些问题
forgetting about our problems at home,
与家人共度这美好时光吧
spending some quality time with the family.
说得对 说得对
You're right, you're right.
我的家人在哪里
Where is my family?
你觉得他们是不是想放我们鸽子
You don't think they're standing us up, do you?
我在超市见到杰的时候
You know, when I saw Jay at the grocery store
问他们会不会来
and asked him if they were coming,
他拿了一颗试吃的肉丸嚼了整整一分钟
he took a sample meatball and chewed it for a full minute
才说来 所以...
before he said yes, so...
你们都还在家啊
You all are still here.
你多常闯进来一次
How often do you break in here?
所以白葡萄酒是你喝的吗
Does that explain the white wine?
我们为此炒了一名清洁工
We fired a cleaning lady.
我还以为你们已经
Listen, I thought you guys
去看莉莉的足球赛了
would already be at Lily's soccer game,
今天早上我家情绪太哀伤
And things have been pretty emotional at my house this morning.
所以我只想在泳池边待上几个小时
I just wanted a couple hours by the pool.
肯定也是克莱尔把冰桶留在按摩浴池边的
Claire must have left the ice bucket by the jacuzzi, too.
我会给清洁工写一封信
I will write the cleaning lady a letter.
你怎么逃掉去看莉莉的比赛的呢
How'd you get out of Lily's game?
我撒谎说艾丽克斯今天离家去学校
I lied and said that Alex was leaving for school today,
结果成真了 所以没我事了
which turned out to be true, so I'm off the hook.
有精彩的地方回头告诉我
You guys let me know what I miss.
你能接电话吗
Could you get that?
-喂 -克莱尔
- Yello? - Claire?
你在那里干什么 我们已经等了...
What are you doing there? We've been waiting --
天啊 天啊 天啊
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
-不敢相信 -真不敢相信
- I don't believe this. - I don't believe this.
居然还要毛巾 他们难道是产婆吗
They want more towels. What are they, midwives?
这边
Here.
不要理会
Just ignore it.
他到底有多少部手机
How many phones does he have?
接电话 随便谁 我...
Pick up. Anybody. I --
我还可以要到更多电话
You know, I could get more phones.
他是不会停的
He's never gonna stop.
米奇尔 你好 我没空说话
Mitchell, hi. Hey, can't talk.
我现在正跟艾丽克斯一起要去大学
I'm just leaving my house right now with alex.
我知道你在老爸家
I know you're at Dad's house.
好吧 听着
Yeah, okay. Um, look.
我什么都不想说 爸爸发生了点意外
I didn't want to say anything. Dad got in an accident.
他没事 不用担心
He's fine. Nothing to worry about,
不过我得走了 拜拜
but I got to go. Bye.
演技真烂
That was pathetic.
我来给你们演示一下该怎么做
Let me show you how it's done.
你好 米奇尔
Hello, Mitchell.
听说我爸出了点小事故
So I hear my dad had a little accident?
是啊 当然了 你爸出的事故
Yes, of course, well, the accident that your father had
其实就是他不小心往自己脚上
is that actually he shot himself
开了一枪
in the foot.
相信我 他相信了
Trust me. He believed me.
你们还有听到电话响起的声音吗
You're not listening to any phone ringings right now,
没有吧
are you?
所以现在变成了
So, this is turning into
泳池边的集体活动了吗
a whole group thing by the pool.
我家的泳池
Our pool.
各位 我刚接到一条小卡的短信
You guys, I just got a text from Cam.
手机给我
Give me that.
"天啊 人家当然希望杰没有事
"Gosh, I sure do hope Jay's all right.
发生这种事情真是好难以置信啊"
It's unbelievable something like that could have happened."
不用谢
You're welcome.
太棒了
Fantastic.
-完美 -我们都解脱了
- It's perfect. - We're all good.
各位 你们最好再听一遍
Well, you guys, you might want to listen again,
不过这次我来演小卡
only this time, I'll be Cam.
"天呐 人家当然希望杰没有事
"Gosh, I sure do hope jay is all right."
发生这种事情真是好"难以置信"啊"
It's unbelievable something like this could happen."
我们惨了
We're screwed.
好 他们现在要过来了
Okay, they're coming,
你敢相信他们居然想跳票吗
but can you believe they were gonna bail?
眼睛看脚下 看脚下
Keep your -- keep your eyes down. Eyes down.
我们有错过一次他们小孩的活动吗
Have we missed a single one of their kids' events?
我们又不是每天闲着没事干
And it's not like we don't have a million things going on right now.
跟上去
Follow through!
对啊 比如上次我们被迫看完
Yeah, like when we had to sit through that
五年级生演的干净版《吉屋出租》
sanitized fifth-grade production of "rent"
他们都得了感冒的那个
where they all got head colds?
腿伸直 给我把腿伸直
Keep your leg straight. Keep your leg straight for me.
-小卡 你能不这样吗 -什么
- Cam, can you not do that? - What?
那个 貌似教练是我 所以...
Well, it's just that, you know, I'm kind of coach, so --
你什么时候不帮我 这种时候帮
It just seems weird that this is the time
感觉有点奇怪
that you're trying to help me.
好吧 我怎么不帮你了
Okay, and in what way am I not helpful?
比如我之前在见一名刚丧偶的客户时
Okay, well, when I'm with a bereaved client, say,
你却觉得那种时刻很适合
and you decide that that's the perfect moment
用你吓死人的演技演一段死去的戏码
for a scenery-chewing death scene.
完全比不上你在处理"艺术房客"相关事宜时
Unlike the tremendous help you've been to me
帮我的大忙啊
running the artful lodger.
你连域名都没注册上
You couldn't even register the domain name.
反正我也不喜欢那个名字
I never liked that name, anyways.
你终于说出来了
And there it is.
我明白了
I see what this is.
-什么 -嫉妒
- What? - Jealousy.
就是啊
Yeah! Yeah.
因为你带的足球队看起来赢不了
'cause your football team can't seem to win,
而我已经四比零了
but here I am 4-0.
好吧 够了
Okay, please. Yeah.
这不过是小女孩玩玩足球
This is little girls' soccer.
都不能算真的运动
It's not even a real sport.
抱歉
Excuse me?
恐怕我必须请您离开了
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
不 我只是...
Oh, no, I was just --
别敬酒不吃吃罚酒
Let's not do this the hard way.
真是太糟糕了
It's the worst of everything.
我们得去看那白痴比赛
We have to go to the damn game.
而且以后他们不可能再相信我们的借口
And they're never gonna believe any of our excuses
哪怕是真的 他们也不会相信了
in the future, even if they're real.
除非...
Unless...
你为什么要这样
Why do you do that?
为什么说完"除非"就不说了
Why do you say "unless" and then pause?
把想法说完整好吗
Just finish the thought.
除非杰真的被枪打中脚了
Unless Jay really gets shot in the foot.
真不敢相信我又得说一遍
I can't believe I'm saying this, once again,
尽管我们结婚才七年
in only seven years of marriage,
但真心求你把枪放下
but please put the gun down.
别这么孬
Don't be a baby.
这只是一把弹子枪
It's a pellet gun.
最多擦伤留个痕
It's just going to be a little nick on the side,
然后我们就可以去看比赛了
and then we go to the game.
他们就会看见你是真的受了伤
They're gonna see that it's true.
他们会因为没有相信我们而感到惭愧
They're gonna feel horrible because they didn't believe us,
然后我们就一整年啥活动都不用去了
and then we don't have to go to anything for a whole year.
不得不说 这有点道理
I have to say, it makes sense.
没有道理
No, it doesn't!
我干嘛不直接贴个绷带一瘸一拐出场呢
Why don't I just bandage my foot up and limp on in there?
不行 不行
No, no, no, no, no.
必须得来真的 不然被他们发现的话
It has to be real because if they catch us faking it,
更难收场
it's going to be worse.
请别拿枪指着我
Please don't point the gun at me.
好了 行了 我爸也说了
Okay, all right, all right. You heard my dad.
把枪挪开
Put the gun away.
我们得 得想想其他办法
We just -- we'll have to think of something else.
该怎么办呢
What to do?
快 开 枪
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
好吧我把枪拿开
Okay, I'll put the gun away.
天哪
No!
我去 你是故意的
No! You did that on purpose!
我都没看着你
I wasn't even looking!
我都转过身了 真对不起
I turned my back on you. I'm so sorry!
看好那个杯子
Watch the sippy cup.
希望你喜欢重金属摇滚乐
I hope you're a heavy metal fan
因为整个"金属"周期表
because all the heavy metals
要挂到你奖杯头顶上了
are going right here above your trophy.
酷 梅西
Cool. Maisie.
话说楼下好像在发邮箱的钥匙
So, I heard they're giving out mailbox keys downstairs,
可以麻烦你去把我们俩的钥匙都领回来吗
and I was thinking maybe you could pick up both of ours?
当然没问题 朋友
Sure thing, friend!
多好的一天 我有了邮箱还有了朋友
What a day -- I've got a mailbox and a friend!
你必须有
You sure do.
你能尽量别这么幸灾乐祸了吗
Could you try not to enjoy this so much?
我这已经是努力忍住了
This is me trying.
这一切到此结束了
This ends now.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
你觉得我要干嘛 我要摆脱她
What do you think I'm doing? I'm getting rid of her.
我要打给我的导师申请换个室友
I'm calling my advisor and getting a new roommate.
-不行 -把手机还给我
- No. - Give that back.
需要提醒你我是黄带吗
Need I remind you I am a yellow belt?
虽然我记不住你那堆丑腰带
I can't keep track of all your ugly belts,
但我就是觉得你不该换室友
but I don't think you should change roommates.
听着 尽管你是我上大学的核心军师
Listen, as much as you're my go-to girl on college advice,
-可我... -天啊
- I really -- - Oh, my God.
你能先闭嘴一会吗
Would you just shut up for a second?
是这样的
Here's the thing --
我也有过这么一个室友
I had a similar experience with a roommate.
她是个讨人厌的"百事通"
She was this annoying little know-it-all
老把我惹毛
who totally got on my nerves.
-是 我知道 -别说话
- Yeah, I get it. - Oh, shh!
我也花了很长时间想要摆脱她
I spent a long time trying to get rid of her
可是直到我发现这个小姑娘
until I realized that that little girl,
其实一直默默地在崇拜着我
in her own way, put me on a pedestal.
我很开心
It felt great.
你刚刚来到一个到处是牛逼人物的地方
You just landed in a world of superstars,
我也不知道你永远不会承认
and I know you'd never admit it,
但你其实还是很害怕的
but you're scared.
拥有一个你自己的拉拉队长并不是坏事
It's not the worst thing to have your own personal cheerleader.
我也开始想念我的拉拉队长了
I miss mine already.
我的五秒应该到了
Well, I guess my five seconds is up.
这么小的浴室虽然不常见
You don't often see a 5/8 bathroom,
但他们也是妥善考量后设计的
but they're highly sought after.
这笔生意已经十拿九稳了 孩子
The deal's in the bag, kid.
我再收收尾 然后我们就走人
I'm just gonna wrap it up, and then we bounce.
我们就蹦起来[走人]
And then we bounce.
去蹦床公园啊
Trampoline park.
你怎么不跟我弹跳式击掌了
How are you not high-boinging me right now?
我想去码头
I was thinking of maybe
和我的小伙伴们碰面
meeting up with my crew at the pier.
没问题 我们蹦完蹦床你再去
Sure thing. After we tramp.
好吧
Fine.
很快 我不再跟爸爸去商店玩了
After a while, I stopped hanging out with my dad at the store.
我开始忙拉拉队的训练
I got busy with cheer practice,
也开始觉得橙子堆的金字塔不再酷炫
and I guess pyramids of oranges don't seem so great
因为我已经叠过人体金字塔了
after you've built pyramids out of man.
我不知道爸爸会不会因我少回家而难过
I don't know if it bothered him that I stopped coming around,
但即使他真的难过 他也从未表露
but if it did, he never let it show.
好了 咱们出发吧
All right. Let's do this.
其实我觉得我
Actually, I think I, uh --
我好像扭到了脚踝
I twisted my ankle
刚才从满是折叠床的房间蹦出来时扭了
jumping out of the way in that room full of murphy beds.
我最好还是别上蹦床了
I probably shouldn't get on a trampoline.
你还是去跟你朋友一起玩吧
You should go hang out with your friends.
-真的吗 -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
想快点去的话 最好是得他们来接你
Might be faster if they come get you, though.
我还得再打扫一遍这房子
I should do one more sweep of the house.
我觉得跟布兰斯顿这家人的生意吹了
I think I lost the Blanstons.
谢谢你 爸爸
Thanks, dad.
债贱
Deuces.
加油 姑娘们
Let's go, girls!
传球 动起来
Pass and move!
运动员不要一直傻站着
The players should never be standing still!
最好的防守就是有力的进攻
The best defense is good offense.
这不对
Well, now, that can't be true.
中场休息
Halftime!
好吧 上半场很棒
Okay, good -- good half!
好 我们落后三分 但是没关系
All right, we're down by three, but that's okay.
看啊 看看是谁终于出现了
Look. Look who finally showed up.
太不容易了
Not easily.
你们也看得到 我的脚伤得很重
As you can see, I have a severely injured foot.
小卡在哪儿
Where is Cam?
他 他被裁判罚出场了
He -- he got banished by the ref.
怎么会这样 说具体点
How did that happen? Be specific.
这有什么
Who cares?
重要的是我实打实地被枪打中了--
The important thing is I did, in fact, shoot myself in the --
省省吧 假伤就够了 别再伤脸皮了
Save it. Don't add insult to fake injury.
-我假伤 -是的
- Fake. - Yeah.
没搞错吧
Seriously?
看看他的小脚趾
Say hello to his little toe.
天哪 你居然真的
Oh, my God. You really
打中了自己的脚
shot myself in the foot.
是啊 是挺吓人的
Yeah, it was so scary.
-还流了好多血 -场面血流成河
- And the blood. - There was so much blood.
可是你们还是来了
But you guys -- you still showed up anyway.
-当然要来了 -一定会来的
- Of course! - Without a doubt.
是妈妈开枪打的杰
Mommy shot Jay.
什么 你不是说是自己打中的吗
I'm sorry, what? I thought you said --
是妈妈打中的杰 克莱尔阿姨说 "打他"
Yeah, mommy shot Jay. Aunt Claire said, "Shoot him."
爸
Dad.
你宁愿中一枪也不想来支持你的孙女吗
You would rather take a bullet than support your granddaughter?
这都是歌洛莉亚的主意
This was really Gloria's idea.
我身边全都是泄密者
I'm surrounded by rats.
米奇尔 听我说
Mitchell, listen to me.
我知道"对不起"一点诚意也没有
I know "I'm sorry" barely covers it,
但是让我来这里看这些小女孩踢球
but it's very difficult for me to come here today
真的太折磨人了
and watch little girls playing soccer
因为我自己的女儿今天离开我去上大学了
on the same day that my little girl left for college.
我也是
Well, me too.
我要看着我的孙女离开
I mean, watching my little grandbaby go off --
别来跟风我的理由
Don't jump on my thing.
抱歉打扰你们
Sorry to interrupt.
其他的父母还有保姆投票了
So, the parents and nannies voted,
我们决定解除你的职务
and we're going to relieve you of your command.
可是我是教练啊
but I'm the coach, so --
现在我才是教练
I'm the coach now.
我真高兴你们能赶上这个场面
Glad you got here in time to see that.
一点也不好笑 克莱尔
It's not funny, Claire.
小卡 你在哪
Cam. Where are you?
我站在停车场 戴着双目镜
In the parking lot with binoculars.
等等
What, when did --
你什么时候买了件军装风外套
When did you buy an army jacket?
不是那个 左边的才是我
Not him, to the left.
看见你了
Oh, hi.
你居然让黛比抢走了你的哨子
So you let Debbie take your whistle?
是啊 也不能怪她 我水平太差
Well, yeah, I can't blame her. I'm a terrible coach.
抱歉我对你这么差
I mean, I'm sorry I-I pushed you away.
别乱说
No, no, no. You hush up.
我才是该道歉的那个
I'm the one who's sorry.
你知道吗 我一直想假装
You know what? I've been trying to pretend like
生活压力没有影响到我 其实我很受影响
the pressure hasn't gotten to me, but it has.
谢天谢地 我也是
Oh, my God. Me too.
我一直以为我们会是那种
I, I always thought we were that couple
患难之中见真情的伴侣 你懂吗
that could rise above tough times, you know?
我不想让我们之间有距离
I just -- I don't want to feel like there's distance between us.
你说什么了 再说一遍
What? Sorry, you're -- say that again.
-你那边信号断了 -我听不见
- You're breaking up. - I didn't hear you.
-什么 -我听见了
-what? Huh? -what? T-there you are.
下半场开始了
Second half, girls.
中场休息结束了 我得走了
Oh, God. Okay. Intermission's over. I got to --
听着 你要把你的指挥权抢回来
Okay, listen up, Bub. You go get your team back.
我们需要这个 今天你得让我们赢
We need this. You're gonna get us a win today.
怎么赢
How?
先去把哨子抢回来
Just go get your whistle back.
看着我
Look at me.
我们能做到
We got this.
-我们落后三球 不过 -你们好啊
- Okay, so we're down by three, but—- - hi!
接下来就交给我吧
So, I got this from here, so --
你在干什么
What do you think you're doing?
完成我的使命
What I was born to do.
靠 我才是教练
I am a coach, damn it.
天哪 抱歉
God. I'm so sorry.
看你扯我的时候 还以为很容易
That came off so much easier when you did it.
变装舞会的经验告诉我们
As our history with costume parties has taught us --
夫夫出击 天下无敌
we shine brightest when we work as a team.
没错
Yeah.
让前锋组成三角形 拉开防线
Okay, have the forwards form a triangle, spread the defense.
前锋上前组成三角形
Okay, forwards, form a triangle.
拉开防线
Spread the defense.
下半场快结束时 我们追平了比分
By late in the half, we had tied the score.
这又一次证明 最好的进攻就是防守
Proving once again, the best offense is a good defense.
这句话就像在说最好的帽子就是鞋子一样
That's like saying the best hat is a shoe.
还剩十秒钟的时候 莉莉迎来了她的机会
Okay, with 10 seconds left, Lily was open on the wing.
让她把球传给莉莉
Now have her pass to Lily.
传球给莉莉
Pass to Lily!
-她传给了莉莉 -我看见了
- She passed to Lily. - I can see.
什么 太棒了
What?! Yes! Yes! Yes!
这都是我的功劳
That was me. I did that.
没错 就是他教的
That was him! He did that.
她不在家这感觉确实有些不同
It does feel different without her here.
没错
Yep.
卢克不在家感觉好安静
Pretty quiet without Luke here, too.
他有说什么时候回来吗
Did he say what time he's coming home?
很快就回来了吧 他给你留了样东西
Soon, I'm sure. Oh, he left you something.
"谢谢你今天带我去看那疯狂的房子
"Thanks for letting me see that crazy house today.
明天想跟我一起建个房子吗"
Feel like building one ourselves tomorrow?"
天哪
What?
他回去把鸭蛋都捡起来了
He went back for the duck eggs.
我们今天在那房子前找到了这些蛋
We found these eggs out in front of the house.
是的 我猜到了
Yeah, honey. I-I-I got it. I got it.
你们俩我最清楚不过了
I know the two of you well enough.
我可以猜到来龙去脉
I can connect the dots.
不过你真的帮了我大忙
But you just really helped me out.
你在打给谁
Who are you --
妈 你怎么又打来了
Again, mom?
艾丽克斯 我知道你说过
Alex, I know you said not to call
没有大事别打给你 但这事很重要
unless it was very important, but this is.
我要知道跟小鸭子有关的一切知识
I need to know everything you can tell me about baby ducks.
痛死了
It stings!
这一点也不性感
This is so not sexy.
现在大家都赞同这个主意了吧
Okay, so we all agree.
每人每年可以缺席一次家中子女的活动
Everybody gets a free pass once a year to miss a kid event.
我听说卢克要组建一个乐队
Ooh, I heard Luke might be forming a boy band,
我想用掉我的那次机会
so I want to get out in front of that.
太好了 这样你就得来参加
Great! That means you'll be available
我一人分饰多角版本的新剧
for my one-man quick-change version
《七对佳偶》
of "Seven brides for seven brothers."
我还是换成缺席这个吧
I'm gonna change my vote.
我选择不要参加这个
Yeah, put me down for missing that, too.
可是你们都没明白呢
No, but you don't understand.
里面所有的角色都是我演的
I-I play all the brides and all the brothers.
我也不去
Make it three.
杰 你一定会来的 对吧
But you'll come, right, Jay?